[Recently,]
[حديثاً،]
[the wealthy family scam was exposed.]
[تم فضح عملية الاحتيال التي قامت بها العائلة الثرية.]
[Xu Meng impersonated Lan Hewei,]
[قام Xu Meng بانتحال شخصية Lan Hewei،]
[playing out a real-life version of the heiress.]
[تجسيد نسخة واقعية من قصة الوريثة.]
[As the true chairman of the Blue Crane Group,]
[بصفته الرئيس الفعلي لمجموعة بلو كرين]
[I hereby announce]
[أعلن بموجب هذا]
[that the resort project]
[أن مشروع المنتجع]
[of the Blue Crane Group will be officially handed over]
[سيتم تسليمها رسمياً إلى مجموعة بلو كرين]
[to the Lin Group.]
[إلى مجموعة لين.]
How could this be?
كيف يمكن أن يكون هذا؟
Honey,
عسل،
try the soup I made.
جرب الحساء الذي أعددته.
you've worked hard.
لقد بذلت جهداً كبيراً.
You try it first.
جربها أولاً.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
Is it good?
هل هو جيد؟
It's the same taste.
إنه نفس المذاق.
Honey,
عسل،
if Xu Meng hadn't interfered,
لو لم يتدخل شو مينغ،
we would have been
كنا سنكون
like this a long time ago.
هكذا منذ زمن بعيد.
Don't worry,
لا تقلق،
I'll make up for everything
سأعوض عن كل شيء
for everything I've lost.
على كل ما فقدته.
As for Xu Meng,
أما بالنسبة لشو مينغ،
I will make her pay for what she did.
سأجعلها تدفع ثمن ما فعلته.
With you here,
بوجودك هنا،
I'm relieved.
أشعر بالارتياح.
Honey,
عسل،
I need to get back to work.
أحتاج للعودة إلى العمل.
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
it's me.
هذا أنا.
Actually, that day,
في الواقع، في ذلك اليوم،
when you spoke,
عندما تحدثت،
I knew
كنت أعرف
the man with bandages was you,
الرجل الذي كان يرتدي الضمادات هو أنت،
not Mengmeng.
لا منجمينج.
Xing,
شينغ،
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
Mengmeng didn't betray you.
لم تخنك منغمينغ.
Everything she did was for you.
كل ما فعلته كان من أجلك.
Don't believe Lin Mojiao.
لا تصدقوا لين موجياو.
He's the one who hurt you.
هو من آذاك.
I'll take you away.
سآخذك بعيداً.
Xing,
شينغ،
Vivi,
أنت تعيش،
let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
Honey.
عسل.
Help my husband.
ساعدوا زوجي.
Help me.
ساعدني.
Honey.
عسل.
Don't be afraid.
لا تخف.
Catch the man who just left my house.
أمسكوا بالرجل الذي غادر منزلي للتو.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
What a loser.
يا له من خاسر!
Lu Xing is so poor.
لو شينغ فقير جداً.
Yeah.
نعم.
His parents divorced and abandoned him.
انفصل والداه عنه وتخلوا عنه.
How is he going to live?
كيف سيعيش؟
Here.
هنا.
Eat it.
تناوله.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Come on.
تعال.
Sit down and eat together.
اجلسوا وتناولوا الطعام معاً.
Sit.
يجلس.
This is for you.
هذا لك.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
My name is Lan Hewei.
اسمي لان هيوي.
What's your name?
ما اسمك؟
I'm Lu Xing.
أنا لو شينغ.
I'm Xu Meng.
أنا شو منغ.
From now on,
من الآن فصاعدًا،
we're friends.
نحن أصدقاء.
Bye.
الوداع.
I'm off. I'm home.
أنا ذاهب. أنا في المنزل.
I'm late again. Sorry.
لقد تأخرت مجدداً. آسف.
Lu Xing,
لو شينغ,
You're late again.
لقد تأخرت مرة أخرى.
I'll take a drink as punishment.
سأتناول مشروباً كعقاب.
Forget it.
انسى ذلك.
Let's drink together.
هيا نشرب معاً.
Here, these are for you.
تفضل، هذه لك.
Thank you, Uncle Hu.
شكراً لك يا عم هو.
It's okay.
لا بأس.
Come on. Let's have a toast.
هيا بنا. لنرفع نخبًا.
I'll finish it.
سأنهي الأمر.
Drink as you please.
اشرب كما تشاء.
Here, try this.
جرب هذا.
What can I do?
ماذا يمكنني أن أفعل؟
I can do nothing.
لا أستطيع فعل شيء.
You dress like an old man all day.
أنت ترتدي ملابس رجل عجوز طوال اليوم.
It's embarrassing to be around me.
من المحرج أن تكون حولي.
I bought these clothes. You can wear them for now.
اشتريت هذه الملابس. يمكنك ارتداؤها الآن.
Buy new ones later.
سأشتري واحدة جديدة لاحقاً.
Here you are.
تفضل.
No one will take care of you if you catch a cold.
لن يعتني بك أحد إذا أصبت بنزلة برد.
Where is this? Why?
أين هذا؟ ولماذا؟
You want to kill me?
أتريد قتلي؟
Why do you have to do this?
لماذا عليك فعل هذا؟
Why do you have to do this to me?
لماذا تفعل بي هذا؟
Let me go. Let go.
دعني أذهب.
There's no reason.
لا يوجد سبب.
Where are you going?
إلى أين أنت ذاهب؟
You look so pretty today.
تبدين جميلة جداً اليوم.
I just want to
أريد فقط أن
go out for a walk.
اخرج في نزهة.
Since you're so pretty,
بما أنكِ جميلة جداً،
why not go with me to see my mother?
لماذا لا تذهب معي لرؤية والدتي؟